What happened?
Now I don't know why it suddenly stopped.
I knew this dagger of yours would definitely betray me.   I had
told you not to bring this car but who
listens to me?  Look, I am stuck in the middle of the forest.  There
is no network either.  Wow,
everything is fine here, friend.
If you say that the petrol is over, I will
beat you badly.  I told you to get it
filled, get it filled.
Hey brother, there was petrol, you miser,
you live on installments.
Keep driving the car by filling petrol in small quantities.
Hey friend, I will have to stop someone and ask for petrol.
You are the only one who demands
this, Panna Lal, the heir of the theft.
Spread spread spread.
Hey, that scooter driver will give you how much petrol.   Are
you a clown and ask for your body?
You only ask for petrol.  I took a lift
home.  Come on brother.
Hey brother, we won't search much.  Hey
brother, take me wherever you want to go.   Will go
there.  That Ram Raghav.
I am hey brother.
Hey, come and sit in the car.  I am
on your junk.  You stay here.  I am taking the leaf.
[screaming sound]
Take it, son.
Hey [music] It'll be fun, right?
Mandaram
[Music]
Mandaramandam